(Sheldon(on video):)is there any peanut brittle
left in that can?
(Leonard(on video):)You mean this weirdly
suspicious one?
(Sheldon(on video):)Yes. Open it and check.
(Leonard(on video):)I don't get it.
(Leonard(on video):)There's actually
peanut brittle in...
(Leonard(on video):)Please go to Mars.
But on a more serious note:
(Sheldon(on video):)The most important reason I want
(Sheldon(on video):)to go to Mars is that
I believe, as a scientist,
(Sheldon(on video):)it's my duty
to push the boundaries
(Sheldon(on video):)of human knowledge forward.
(Sheldon(on video):)Now, I know that life on Mars
will be difficult.
(Sheldon(on video):)But life here on Earth
is no picnic.
(Sheldon(on video):)Also, picnics are no picnic.
(Sheldon(on video):)Where should we go for lunch?
(Sheldon(on video):)Oh, I know, the ground.
(Sheldon(on video):)In conclusion,
(Sheldon(on video):)thank you for considering me
(Sheldon(on video):)for this journey of a lifetime.